question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The Earth revolves around the Sun in one year.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Albert Einstein won a noble prize for his theory of relativity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The shape of the Earth is a perfect sphere.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Sugar contains fat.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
